<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on sakibNazmush</title>
    <link>e.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on sakibNazmush</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 09:56:53 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="e.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced WordPress Development</title>
      <link>e.com/certificates/certificate2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/certificates/certificate2/</guid>
      <description>In this course I&amp;rsquo;ve learned:&#xA;Understanding of HTML for structuring web content. CSS for styling and layout customization. JavaScript knowledge for enhancing interactivity and user experience. Advanced PHP skills, including Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). Competence in jQuery for simplifying JavaScript tasks. Bootstrap proficiency for responsive and mobile-friendly design. MySQL for efficient database management. Theme customization using Elementor and Divi builders. WooCommerce, Contact Form 7 Eexpertise in plugin development to extend WordPress functionality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS50’s Introduction to Databases with SQL</title>
      <link>e.com/certificates/certificate1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/certificates/certificate1/</guid>
      <description>This is CS50’s introduction to databases using a language called SQL. In this course I learned:&#xA;Introduction to databases using SQL in CS50. CRUD operations in relational databases (create, read, update, delete). Modeling real-world entities and relationships using tables. What is ERD Utilizing appropriate types, triggers, and constraints. Normalizing data to eliminate redundancies and reduce errors. Joining tables with primary and foreign keys. Automating searches with views and expediting with indexes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python for Beginners</title>
      <link>e.com/certificates/certificate4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/certificates/certificate4/</guid>
      <description>Python Course Certificate I completed a Python programming course where I gained foundational knowledge in several key areas:&#xA;Programming Fundamentals: Learned the basics of coding, including variables, data types, and control flow structures. Data Structures: Explored lists, tuples, and dictionaries for effective data organization and manipulation. Functions and Modules: Mastered the creation and utilization of functions, as well as the organization of code into modular structures. Control Flow: Developed an understanding of if statements and loops to control the flow of program execution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Gun - Maverick</title>
      <link>e.com/watchlist/movie2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/watchlist/movie2/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One</title>
      <link>e.com/watchlist/movie3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/watchlist/movie3/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expend4bles</title>
      <link>e.com/watchlist/movie1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/watchlist/movie1/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 48 Laws of Power</title>
      <link>e.com/reading_list/book3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/reading_list/book3/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Comapny Website</title>
      <link>e.com/projects/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/projects/project1/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A cleaning company website with booking and payment gateway functionalities. See here: Behance&#xA;Greetings!&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to present my latest solo project – a dynamic WordPress website that not only showcases my passion for web development but also seamlessly integrates advanced booking functionalities and secure payment gateways. Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP, I&amp;rsquo;ve created a versatile platform that goes beyond the ordinary.&#xA;Key Accomplishments:&#xA;🎨 Elementor Expertise: I&amp;rsquo;ve harnessed the power of Elementor, a cornerstone in my toolkit, to design visually stunning layouts that captivate visitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1. WordPress - A Versatile Platform for Seamless Web Development</title>
      <link>e.com/articles/art1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/articles/art1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction WordPress, a powerful and versatile content management system (CMS), has become the go-to choice for website development due to its ease of use, extensive features, and robust community support. With over 40% of the web powered by WordPress, it has evolved from a simple blogging tool to a full-fledged CMS used by individuals, businesses, and enterprises worldwide.&#xA;Installation Installation of WordPress is a straightforward process, making it accessible to users of all levels of technical expertise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. Web Development - A Journey Through Time and Technology</title>
      <link>e.com/articles/art2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/articles/art2/</guid>
      <description>Past: The inception of web development dates back to the early 1990s when the World Wide Web became publicly accessible. Initially, websites were simple, static pages coded in HTML. The rudimentary nature of these early websites marked the humble beginnings of web development. As the internet gained popularity, the demand for dynamic and interactive websites led to the introduction of technologies like CSS for styling and JavaScript for enhancing user experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>গৃহদাহ</title>
      <link>e.com/reading_list/book1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/reading_list/book1/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>দ্য টুয়েন্টিয়েথ ওয়াইফ</title>
      <link>e.com/reading_list/book2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/reading_list/book2/</guid>
      <description>coming soon </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Fundamentals</title>
      <link>e.com/certificates/certificate5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/certificates/certificate5/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript Fundamentals I successfully completed a foundational JavaScript course, earning a certificate to validate my understanding of key concepts. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of what I learned:&#xA;Basic Syntax: Understanding variables, data types, and operators. Writing clean and effective JavaScript code. Control Flow: Using conditional statements (if, else) for decision-making. Employing loops (for, while) for iterative processes. Functions: Defining and calling functions. Understanding parameters and return values. Arrays and Objects: Working with arrays and objects to organize data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Hour GIT started with GitHub</title>
      <link>e.com/certificates/certificate3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>e.com/certificates/certificate3/</guid>
      <description>Git and GitHub Basics I successfully completed a comprehensive Git and GitHub course, earning a certificate to validate my understanding. Here&amp;rsquo;s a brief overview of what I learned:&#xA;Git Basics: Understanding repositories, commits, branches, and merges. Creating and cloning repositories, making and managing commits. Utilizing branches for parallel development and merging changes. GitHub Integration: Leveraging GitHub for collaborative development. Initiating and managing pull requests to propose and merge changes. Using GitHub as a remote repository for seamless collaboration.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
