<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on sakibsNaz/&gt;</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on sakibsNaz/&gt;</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wild Robot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/wild-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/wild-robot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;plot&#34;&gt;Plot&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shipwrecked on a deserted island, a robot named Roz must learn to adapt to its new surroundings. Building relationships with the native animals, Roz soon develops a parental bond with an orphaned gosling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to install Time Doctor 2 on Manjaro Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-install-timedoctor-2-on-manjaro-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-install-timedoctor-2-on-manjaro-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;installing-time-doctor-2-on-manjaro-linux&#34;&gt;Installing Time Doctor 2 on Manjaro Linux&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s work environment, keeping track of time and staying productive is really important, whether you’re working on a team or as a freelancer. Time Doctor 2 is a helpful time tracking tool that lets you record how much time you spend on tasks, manage your work, and even track breaks. It helps people and businesses make the most of their time and get more done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Support Agent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/technical-support-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/technical-support-agent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-i-do&#34;&gt;What I Do&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Provide technical support and troubleshooting assistance for the Zepto Product Personalizer app to ensure proper user experience for Shopify store owners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resolve customer inquiries, issues, and complaints efficiently via email, chat, and phone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with the development team to report bugs, suggest improvements, and implement solutions based on user feedback.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Update and writing documentation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;apps-in-shopify-app-store&#34;&gt;Apps in Shopify App Store&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.shopify.com/product-personalizer&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;Zepto Product Personalizer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.shopify.com/popman-popups-social&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;PopMan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;official-website&#34;&gt;Official Website&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://zeptoapps.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;Zepto Apps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person of Interest</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/person-of-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/person-of-interest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;plot&#34;&gt;Plot&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The series centers on a mysterious reclusive billionaire computer programmer, Harold Finch, who has developed a computer program for the federal government known as &amp;ldquo;The Machine&amp;rdquo; that is capable of collating all sources of information to predict terrorist acts and to identify people planning them. The series raises an array of moral issues, from questions of privacy and &amp;ldquo;The greater good&amp;rdquo;, the concept of justifiable homicide, and problems caused by working with limited information programs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUD - PHP &amp; MySQL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/grade-crud-using-php-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/grade-crud-using-php-mysql/</guid>
      <description>Grade system CRUD using PHP and MySQL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interstate 60</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/interstate-60/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/interstate-60/</guid>
      <description>Cyclone Remal plunged us into darkness for nearly 20 hours. Trapped indoors, I stumbled upon this movie&amp;hellip; and wow, what a movie!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flex Akademi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/flexakademi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/flexakademi/</guid>
      <description>A learning management system. Made using Elementor, Tutor LMS and some other essential plugins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to setup WooCommerce with Tutor LMS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-setup-woocommerce-with-tutor-lms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-setup-woocommerce-with-tutor-lms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tutor LMS has some excellent features and one of them is integration with WooCommerce. For paid course it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a mandatatory feature of Learning Management Systems. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step by step way to enable the WooCommerce as an ecommerce engine:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dr1nwz8am/image/upload/v1715360755/settings_tutor_lms_sakibsnaz_hy2mze.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, from Tutor LMS, click on Settings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dr1nwz8am/image/upload/v1715360269/tutor_lms_monetization_sakibsnaz_tutor_lms_integration_with_woocommerce_dk63w9.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From settings, click on Monetization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/dr1nwz8am/image/upload/v1715360269/search_engine_sakibsnaz_tutor_lms_integration_with_woocommerce_mkic5o.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After clicking Monetization, click on &amp;lsquo;Select e-commerce engine&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate Hugo site from Vercel to another Hosting/Domain | Web Dev</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/migrate-hugo-site-from-vercel-to-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/migrate-hugo-site-from-vercel-to-hosting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out my recent YouTube video for a quick guide on smoothly shifting your Hugo site from Vercel to hosting. This move can save costs and give you more control over your website. First, make sure your site&amp;rsquo;s on GitHub, then pick a hosting service that fits your needs. Set up your hosting, move your files over, and solve any problems that pop up. Test everything out to make sure your site works well in its new home. For more details, watch the video and make the switch with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TourVista</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/tourvista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/tourvista/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;-tourvista-where-adventure-begins-explore-book-and-make-memories-effortlessly&#34;&gt;🚀 TourVista: Where adventure begins. Explore, book, and make memories effortlessly.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sakibsnaz.com/tourvista&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;case-study-tourvista---a-travel-booking-platform-makeover&#34;&gt;Case Study: TourVista - A Travel Booking Platform Makeover&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;client-background&#34;&gt;Client Background&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TourVista, a growing travel startup, came to us with a dream: to simplify how people book and enjoy travel adventures. They wanted a website where anyone could effortlessly plan trips, book accommodations, and find exciting activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;challenges&#34;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile-Friendly Design:&lt;/strong&gt; Creating a responsive website that delivers a seamless experience across all devices.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning-Fast Performance:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensuring fast loading times to keep users engaged and minimize bounce rates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimizing User Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; Designing an intuitive interface that simplifies travel booking and exploration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boosting Search Engine Visibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Improving search engine rankings to attract more organic traffic and customers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-approach&#34;&gt;Our Approach&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Custom Design with Elementor:&lt;/strong&gt; We used Elementor and Essential Addons for Elementor to build a beautiful and user-friendly site that showcases TourVista&amp;rsquo;s travel offerings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easy Booking with WP Travel Engine:&lt;/strong&gt; By integrating WP Travel Engine and its simple booking widgets, we made booking trips a breeze.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed Boost with LiteSpeed Cache:&lt;/strong&gt; We added LiteSpeed Cache to make the site load faster, ensuring a smooth experience for users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Better Search Results with Yoast SEO:&lt;/strong&gt; We optimized TourVista&amp;rsquo;s site to show up higher in search results, bringing in more visitors.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;results&#34;&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seamless Mobile Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; TourVista now offers a seamless browsing and booking experience across all devices, leading to increased user engagement and satisfaction.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning-Fast Performance:&lt;/strong&gt; With optimized performance and fast loading times, TourVista keeps users engaged and reduces bounce rates, resulting in higher conversion rates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced User Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; The intuitive interface and streamlined booking process make it easy for users to plan and book their travel adventures, driving customer retention and loyalty.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved Search Visibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Through effective SEO strategies and monitoring with Google Search Console, TourVista has achieved higher rankings and increased organic traffic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By focusing on simplicity and user experience, we&amp;rsquo;ve transformed TourVista into a go-to destination for travel planning. With a faster, more user-friendly site and improved search visibility, TourVista is ready to make waves in the travel industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Empires - Ottoman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/rise-of-empires-ottoman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/rise-of-empires-ottoman/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A two-season, twelve-episode TV series based on historical events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Booking Plugins for WordPress in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/best-booking-plugins-for-wordpress-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/best-booking-plugins-for-wordpress-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out the 5 Best Booking Plugins for WordPress in 2024 to manage appointments, reservations, and schedules with ease. These plugins are ideal for businesses like salons, hotels, clinics, and more, offering user-friendly features such as customizable booking forms, calendar synchronization, payment options, and automated reminders to improve customer experience and streamline your booking process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Comprehensive Guide to Booking Plugins for WordPress! In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, managing appointments and reservations efficiently is crucial for businesses of all sizes. WordPress offers a plethora of booking plugins, each with its unique features and functionalities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Top 5 WordPress LMS Plugins for Enhanced Online Learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/5-best-lms-plugin-for-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/5-best-lms-plugin-for-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Diving into the world of online education, we find ourselves confronted with a myriad of options to amplify our teaching prowess. Among these tools, Learning Management Systems (LMS) reign supreme, acting as the cornerstone of virtual classrooms. In the bustling ecosystem of WordPress, where innovation meets accessibility, a plethora of LMS plugins await exploration, promising to revolutionize the digital learning landscape. Join us as we embark on a journey to uncover the top five contenders that stand tall in the realm of WordPress LMS plugins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incendies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/incendies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/incendies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;plot&#34;&gt;Plot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A dying mother writes to her children Jeanne and Simon requesting them to fulfil her last wishes. Following her instructions, they discover a world full of hatred, differences and love.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;some-dialogues-from-this-masterpiece&#34;&gt;Some dialogues from this masterpiece:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One plus one, does it make one?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Death is never the end of the story. It always leaves tracks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nothing is more beautiful than being together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Childhood is like a knife stuck in the throat, which cannot be removed easily.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Grid system and Responsive design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certificates/crash-course-on-grid-system-and-responsive-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certificates/crash-course-on-grid-system-and-responsive-design/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Support Skills</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/customer-support-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/customer-support-skills/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Course&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;customer-support-skills&#34;&gt;Customer Support Skills&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Academy&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freshworks Academy&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Platform&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Udemy&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Learning Outcome&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to write clear and effective email that clearly and professionally help customers to solve their issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to manage difficult and tough conversations with confidence. No matter what keeping the conversation calm and polite.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Showing empathy. Understanding and respond the customer emotions, making them feel safe and valued. Make them comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make a email or response templates for the common issues. That will help instantly calm the tough customers. Later handle with more confidence and care.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Course Link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udemy.com/course/customer-support-skills/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;Customer Support Skills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI/UX For Beginners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certificates/ui_ux_for_beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certificates/ui_ux_for_beginners/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love building websites with WordPress, and I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about making them user-friendly. Recently, I took a beginner&amp;rsquo;s course on UI and UX from Great Learning to dive deeper into creating great user experiences. This course gave me awesome tips on how to design interfaces that are not only easy to use but also look fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through my journey as a developer, I&amp;rsquo;ve realized how important it is to balance functionality with design. With my skills in WordPress and my new knowledge of UI/UX, I can create websites that not only look good but also make users happy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exclusive Webinar on WordPress Plugin Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/webinar-on-wp-plugin-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/webinar-on-wp-plugin-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently had the amazing opportunity to attend A webinar organized by &lt;a href=&#34;https://wedevs.academy/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;weDevs Academy&lt;/a&gt; on WordPress plugin development covers the best coding practices, career opportunities, and a Q&amp;amp;A session dedicated to this field. The session covered aspects such as career opportunities for developers, the current state of WordPress plugin development, and additional in-depth discussions on relevant subjects. hosted by  and featuring industry leaders. It was an incredibly valuable chance to learn from senior experts like Hasin bhai, Nahid bhai, and Tareq bhai. My sincere thanks to weDevs and the wonderful host, Raad bhai, for providing such a fantastic learning experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Reacher</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/jack-reacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/jack-reacher/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;release-date&#34;&gt;Release Date&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;December 19, 2012&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cast&#34;&gt;Cast&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tom Cruise, Rosamund Pike, Lee Child, Alexia Fast, Warner Herzog and Jai Courtney&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;plot&#34;&gt;Plot&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When a former US Army sniper, James Barr, is accused of killing five people, Jack Reacher, a former Military Police officer, takes it upon himself to investigate the case.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;sequel&#34;&gt;Sequel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jack Reacher: Never Go Back&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;review&#34;&gt;Review&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jack Reacher is an old-fashioned type of guy — he doesn’t use a cell phone or credit cards, he travels by bus — and the first film adaptation of one of Lee Child’s Reacher novels has a correspondingly gritty, low-tech, real-muscle appeal. Tom Cruise might not be the 6-foot-5 rock described in the books, but he makes the title role fit him like a latex glove in a winning turn that could spawn a popular new franchise for the star, if public reaction to Christopher McQuarrie’s film is as strong as its fun quotient warrants.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Developer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/fiverr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/fiverr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Developer Intern</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/softtechit-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/softtechit-intern/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aenean euismod ipsum at diam cursus tristique. In a ullamcorper risus. Nam dapibus dolor et pellentesque condimentum. Nunc nec iaculis magna. In volutpat vitae augue eget pharetra. Quisque consectetur, nunc pulvinar lobortis laoreet, erat diam maximus elit, non egestas lectus lectus sed eros.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aenean euismod ipsum at diam cursus tristique. In a ullamcorper risus. Nam dapibus dolor et pellentesque condimentum. Nunc nec iaculis magna. In volutpat vitae augue eget pharetra. Quisque consectetur, nunc pulvinar lobortis laoreet, erat diam maximus elit, non egestas lectus lectus sed eros.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced WordPress Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certificates/advanced-wordpress-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certificates/advanced-wordpress-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this course I&amp;rsquo;ve learned:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of &lt;strong&gt;HTML&lt;/strong&gt; for structuring web content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CSS&lt;/strong&gt; for styling and layout customization.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JavaScript&lt;/strong&gt; knowledge for enhancing interactivity and user experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advanced &lt;strong&gt;PHP&lt;/strong&gt; skills, including &lt;strong&gt;Object-Oriented Programming&lt;/strong&gt; (OOP).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Competence in &lt;strong&gt;jQuery&lt;/strong&gt; for simplifying JavaScript tasks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bootstrap&lt;/strong&gt; proficiency for &lt;strong&gt;responsive&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;mobile-friendly&lt;/strong&gt; design.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MySQL&lt;/strong&gt; for efficient database management.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Theme customization using &lt;strong&gt;Elementor&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Divi&lt;/strong&gt; builders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WooCommerce&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Contact Form 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Eexpertise in &lt;strong&gt;plugin development&lt;/strong&gt; to extend WordPress functionality.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Skillful in both &lt;strong&gt;theme development&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;child theme&lt;/strong&gt; creation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Well-versed in integrating and customizing various WordPress themes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Applied knowledge in creating &lt;strong&gt;dynamic&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;interactive&lt;/strong&gt; web applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Completed assignments and projects demonstrating real-world application of skills.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m excited to apply my advanced WordPress knowledge in developing robust and feature-rich websites. Eager to contribute to projects that demand high-level customization and optimization!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS50’s Introduction to Databases with SQL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certificates/cs50-sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certificates/cs50-sql/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is CS50’s introduction to databases using a language called SQL. In this course I learned:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Introduction to databases using SQL in CS50.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CRUD&lt;/strong&gt; operations in relational databases (create, read, update, delete).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Modeling real-world entities and relationships using tables.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What is &lt;strong&gt;ERD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Utilizing appropriate &lt;strong&gt;types&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;triggers&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;constraints&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Normalizing data to eliminate &lt;strong&gt;redundancies&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;reduce errors&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Joining tables with primary and foreign keys.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automating searches with views and expediting with indexes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Connecting SQL with languages like &lt;strong&gt;Python&lt;/strong&gt; and Java. But I choose Python.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Beginning with &lt;strong&gt;SQLite&lt;/strong&gt; for portability, ending with &lt;strong&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;MySQL for scalability&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Assignments inspired by &lt;strong&gt;real-world datasets&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m eager to leverage my SQL knowledge in managing and extracting insights from databases. Excited to contribute to projects that involve effective data management!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Gun - Maverick</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/top-gun-maverick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/top-gun-maverick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/mission-impossible-dr-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/mission-impossible-dr-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expend4bles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/expend4bles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/expend4bles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 48 Laws of Power</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/the-48-laws-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/the-48-laws-of-power/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Comapny Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/cleaning-company-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/cleaning-company-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;-a-cleaning-company-website-with-booking-and-payment-gateway-functionalities&#34;&gt;🚀 A cleaning company website with booking and payment gateway functionalities.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.behance.net/gallery/179678439/Cleaning-Company-Website&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; &gt;Behance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greetings!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to present my latest solo project – a dynamic WordPress website that not only showcases my passion for web development but also seamlessly integrates advanced booking functionalities and secure payment gateways. Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP, I&amp;rsquo;ve created a versatile platform that goes beyond the ordinary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Accomplishments&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🎨 &lt;strong&gt;Elementor Expertise&lt;/strong&gt;: I&amp;rsquo;ve harnessed the power of Elementor, a cornerstone in my toolkit, to design visually stunning layouts that captivate visitors. This ensures not just functionality but an immersive and engaging user interface.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>পার্থিব</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/parthib-by-shirshendu-mukhopaddhay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/parthib-by-shirshendu-mukhopaddhay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;রভউ&#34;&gt;রিভিউ&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;বইটির নাম পার্থিব না দিয়ে অপার্থিব দিলে হয়তো অনুভূতিটা শুধু নাম দিয়েই প্রকাশ করে দিতে পারতাম।&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>গৃহদাহ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/grihodaho/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/grihodaho/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>দ্য টুয়েন্টিয়েথ ওয়াইফ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/the-twentieth-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/the-twentieth-wife/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Originals - How Non-Conformists Move the World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/originals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/originals/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Knight Trilogy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/the-dark-knight-trilogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/the-dark-knight-trilogy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shawshank Redemption</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/the-shawshank-redemption/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/watchlist/the-shawshank-redemption/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>অপেক্ষা</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/opekkha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/opekkha/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alchemist</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/the-alchemist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading_list/the-alchemist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;coming-soon&#34;&gt;coming soon&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
