<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on sakibsNaz/&gt;</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on sakibsNaz/&gt;</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to install Time Doctor 2 on Manjaro Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-install-timedoctor-2-on-manjaro-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-install-timedoctor-2-on-manjaro-linux/</guid>
      <description>Installing Time Doctor 2 on Manjaro Linux In today’s work environment, keeping track of time and staying productive is really important, whether you’re working on a team or as a freelancer. Time Doctor 2 is a helpful time tracking tool that lets you record how much time you spend on tasks, manage your work, and even track breaks. It helps people and businesses make the most of their time and get more done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to setup WooCommerce with Tutor LMS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-setup-woocommerce-with-tutor-lms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-setup-woocommerce-with-tutor-lms/</guid>
      <description>Tutor LMS has some excellent features and one of them is integration with WooCommerce. For paid course it&amp;rsquo;s kind of a mandatatory feature of Learning Management Systems. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step by step way to enable the WooCommerce as an ecommerce engine:&#xA;Step 1:&#xA;First, from Tutor LMS, click on Settings.&#xA;Step 2:&#xA;From settings, click on Monetization.&#xA;Step 3:&#xA;After clicking Monetization, click on &amp;lsquo;Select e-commerce engine&amp;rsquo;&#xA;Step 4:&#xA;Click &amp;lsquo;Select Option&amp;rsquo; for expand it and choose &amp;lsquo;WooCommerce&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate Hugo site from Vercel to another Hosting/Domain | Web Dev</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/migrate-hugo-site-from-vercel-to-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/migrate-hugo-site-from-vercel-to-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Check out my recent YouTube video for a quick guide on smoothly shifting your Hugo site from Vercel to hosting. This move can save costs and give you more control over your website. First, make sure your site&amp;rsquo;s on GitHub, then pick a hosting service that fits your needs. Set up your hosting, move your files over, and solve any problems that pop up. Test everything out to make sure your site works well in its new home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Booking Plugins for WordPress in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/best-booking-plugins-for-wordpress-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/best-booking-plugins-for-wordpress-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Introduction BookingPress WooCommerce Bookings Bookly Pro Amelia Simply Schedule Appointments Conclusion Introduction Welcome to the Comprehensive Guide to Booking Plugins for WordPress! In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, managing appointments and reservations efficiently is crucial for businesses of all sizes. WordPress offers a plethora of booking plugins, each with its unique features and functionalities.&#xA;This guide aims to provide you with insights into the top booking plugins available for WordPress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Top 5 WordPress LMS Plugins for Enhanced Online Learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/5-best-lms-plugin-for-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/5-best-lms-plugin-for-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Diving into the world of online education, we find ourselves confronted with a myriad of options to amplify our teaching prowess. Among these tools, Learning Management Systems (LMS) reign supreme, acting as the cornerstone of virtual classrooms. In the bustling ecosystem of WordPress, where innovation meets accessibility, a plethora of LMS plugins await exploration, promising to revolutionize the digital learning landscape. Join us as we embark on a journey to uncover the top five contenders that stand tall in the realm of WordPress LMS plugins.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
